<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EcoScout</string>
    <string name="eco_scout_text">A Click for Clean, A Future for Green!</string>

    //bwc (Barangay-Wide Cleanup)
    <string name="bwcLocation">Golden Country Homes
\nBatangas City
\nSouth Luzon</string>
    <string name="bwcDesc">A barangay-led initiative to clean up streets, drainage systems, and public spaces.
\nVolunteers will also conduct door-to-door education on waste segregation and recycling.</string>

    //ccd (Coastal Cleanup Drive)
    <string name="ccdLocation">White Beach
\nBoracay
\nAklan</string>
    <string name="ccdDesc">Join us in preserving the pristine beauty of Boracay!
\nVolunteers will help clean the coastline and underwater areas.
\nScuba divers and snorkelers are welcome.
\nSnacks and certificates will be provided.</string>

    //mmrc (Metro Manila River Cleanup)
    <string name="mmrcLocation">Pasig River
\nMetro Manila
\nPhilippines</string>
    <string name="mmrcDesc">A large-scale effort to clean up the iconic Pasig River.
\nVolunteers will work on removing plastic waste and other debris from riverbanks.
\nIncludes an environmental talk by local eco-warriors.</string>

    //mtc (Mountain Trails Cleanup)
    <string name="mtcLocation">Mt. Pulag
\nBenguet
\nCordillera Region</string>
    <string name="mtcDesc">Help maintain the beauty of Mt. Pulag\'s trails!
\nThis cleanup targets the camping and hiking routes.
\nParticipants will also receive a guided hike and eco-tour as part of the event.</string>

    //upc (Urban Park Cleanup)
    <string name="upcLocation">Quezon Memorial Circle
\nQuezon City
\nMetro Manila</string>
    <string name="upcDesc">A community event focused on cleaning up litter in the park.
\nFollowed by a tree-planting activity.
\nPerfect for families and student organizations.</string>

    //mrc (Mangrove Reforestation and Cleanup)
    <string name="mrcLocation">Banacon Island
\nBohol
\nCentral Visayas</string>
    <string name="mrcDesc">Volunteers will help clean up the mangrove areas.
\nPlant mangrove saplings to protect the coastline from erosion.
\nProvide habitat for marine life.</string>

    //bcm (Beach Cleanup Marathon)
    <string name="bcmLocation">Cloud 9 Beach
\nSiargao
\nSurigao del Norte</string>
    <string name="bcmDesc">A day-long beach cleanup event focused on the surfing areas of Siargao.
\nSurf lessons will be offered at a discount for volunteers after the cleanup.</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">150271275690-6rbvnilj4hgm54i36um8qnatsvm2tvab.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>

    //crc (Coral Reef Cleanup)
    <string name="crcLocation">Apo Island
\nDauin
\nNegros Oriental</string>
    <string name="crcDesc">Divers and snorkelers are invited to join this underwater cleanup event aimed at removing trash from the coral reef area.
\nThis event is part of World Oceans Day celebrations.
\nParticipants will receive free environmental conservation workshops.</string>

    //plc (Plaza Cleanup Drive)
    <string name="pcdLocation">Rizal Park
\nManila
\nPhilippines</string>
    <string name="pcdDesc">Volunteers will assist in cleaning litter and maintaining flowerbeds in one of the most historic parks in the Philippines.
\nA short heritage tour of Rizal Park will follow the cleanup activity.</string>

    //iwc (Island-wide Cleanup)
    <string name="iwcLocation">Bantayan Island
\nCebu
\nCentral Visayas</string>
    <string name="iwcDesc">A community-led effort to clean beaches, roadsides, and public areas on Bantayan Island.
\nLocal food and cultural performances will be provided as a token of appreciation for volunteers.</string>

    //llc (Lake Cleanup)
    <string name="lctlLocation">Taal Lake
\nBatangas
\nCalabarzon</string>
    <string name="lctlDesc">Help clean up Taal Lake and its surrounding areas while learning about the ecosystem of this critical water body.
\nIncludes an eco-tour of nearby fishing villages.</string>

    //esc (Estero Cleanup)
    <string name="ecbLocation">Estero de Binondo
\nBinondo
\nManila</string>
    <string name="ecbDesc">This cleanup focuses on one of Manila\'s historic waterways.
\nVolunteers will work on removing debris and water hyacinths clogging the estero.
\nThe event includes a discussion on urban waterway management.</string>

    //hlc (Highland Cleanup)
    <string name="hcsLocation">Sagada
\nMountain Province
\nCordillera Region</string>
    <string name="hcsDesc">A cleanup initiative targeting the scenic mountain trails and local villages of Sagada.
\nParticipants will also get a chance to visit famous attractions such as the Hanging Coffins and Echo Valley.</string>

</resources>